<resources>
    <string name="app_name">प्रवाह 2018</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">SIGN IN</string>
    <string name="title_activity_theme1"></string>
    <string name="theme">
       "Rich with the culture of centuries and ages and bestowed upon with the best of scenic beauties is the Indian state of Uttar Pradesh.\n\n\n"
       "Home to the largest population share in the country, this land of the gods is surely anticipated to make heads turn.\n\n\n"
       "And keeping this beauty as the main theme, AKTU brings to you the cultural extravaganza Pravah..\n\n"
          "WELCOME ALL"
    </string>
    <string name="band">
        "The strings of a guitar, beats on a drum and the melody of a flute plus some enthralling energy, all goes into the abnormal pumping of hearts.
The battle for bands shall be one major event type and annex a stage like no other.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"It will be a Group event. Team can comprise of 4-6 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants can sing on the song of their own choice.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Duration: 10-12 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own musical instruments.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="play">
       "Acting, as they say is the language of motions, of emotions and of some high-spirited performers who dare to give a damn. A skit contest, thus awaits all you amateurs loaded with skills and a message to share.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"It will be a Group event.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 8 - 10 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Duration: 10 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all.\n"</i>
    </string>
    <string name="fashion">
       "An affair carrying exuberance like no other, a show of enticing fashion, of beaming confidence, and of the best new trends expects us all. Open both for young men and women, the Fashion Jalwa is gonna be one big spectacle.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 2 members (1M/1F).\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Materials required for the contest must be brought by the contestants themselves.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Detailed rules will be announced prior to each round.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all.\n"</i>
    </string>
    <string name="comedy">
       "Something that asks for a not a lot of skill, but that humour and the actor in you to stand out. Show up with your rib-tickling mimics and acts of comedy that lifts the mood and are a treat altogether.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 1-2 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Duration: 3 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all.\n"</i>
    </string>
    <string name="singing">
       "They say, music is the language of the soul. That pious form of art that counts and leaves am impression to last. And to create music, be it vocals or instruments, your voice or your tunes, it all counts. And it does make a mark. So, Pravah, brings to you singing competition in the confines of Solo, Group, and Duet. Language shall be English or Hindi.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"For Solo, Duet and Group singing team can comprise of 1, 2 and 4-6 members respectively.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants can sing on the song of their own choice.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Duration: 3 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own song in a pen drive.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own instruments/karaoke if required.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="dance">
       "Probably the best way to express, to show-up feelings and thoughts, and to mesmerize the onlookers is to dance. And the expressive youth of ours is no less in shaking up legs and leaving the audiences in awe. Pravah, AKTU's cultural extravaganza also brings up opportunities in great number for the dancing enthusiasts, be it Solo, Duet or Group Dance Contests.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"For Solo, Duet and Group dance team can comprise of 1, 2 and 6-8 members respectively.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants can dance on the song of their own choice.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Duration: 3 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own song in a pen drive.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="collage">
        "To put pieces together , and come up with an artistic exploit of the highest kind is what a collage is all about. So, do show up in a team of two, and unveil your creativity to stir minds and bunch up some appealing art.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 2 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants will be given a theme.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The Design using the theme accurately will be awarded extra points.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Duration: 60 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Marks will be deducted if time limit is exceeded.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own materials.\n"</i>
        <b>"7. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="tshirt">
        "The best of creative carvers are up front for the T-shirt designing competition, as the canvas now shifts to an apparel. Something worth remembrance will be made, with just a few colours and sheer imagination.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 2 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants will be given a theme.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The Design using the theme accurately will be awarded extra points.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Duration: 60 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Marks will be deducted if time limit is exceeded.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own materials.\n"</i>
        <b>"7. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="poster">
        "Bring out the creativity in you, young artists and design a beauty that appeals the art-pundits and the masses concurrently. Team of two, shall work hard and prepare the best of all that a poster can be.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 2 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants will be given a theme.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The design using the theme accurately will be awarded extra points.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Duration: 60 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Marks will be deducted if time limit is exceeded.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own materials.\n"</i>
        <b>"7. "</b><i>"Any pre-prepared work shall lead to disqualification.\n"</i>
        <b>"8. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="face">
        "Life isn't about what we're born, it rather is about what new can we incorporate. To decorate a face, with glitter and an entirely different sort of magic is what's expected out of the Face Painting Contest. Do come in a team of two, and let your awesomeness let loose.\n\n\n"
         <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 2 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants will be given a theme.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The design using the theme accurately will be awarded extra points.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Duration: 60 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Marks will be deducted if time limit is exceeded.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own materials.\n"</i>
        <b>"7. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="rangoli">
        "The beauty of laying colours on a canvas encompass all, what if this upscaled to a dimension more, defining that extraordinary confine of art is the 3D Rangoli/Painting contest. Wherein, a team of 4 can choose the requisites and bring out the best of art.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 4 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Participants will be given a theme on which they will be required to make a rangoli.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"The rangoli designed using the theme accurately will be awarded extra points.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"Duration: 90 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"5. "</b><i>"Marks will be deducted if time limit is exceeded.\n"</i>
        <b>"6. "</b><i>"Participants should bring their own materials.\n"</i>
        <b>"7. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="mehandi">
        "The beautiful Mehandi smeared hands of a bride turn heads of people from all around the world. And such mesmerizing designs is what the budding artists are to come up with. Thereby, also preserving traditional Indian grace.\n\n\n"
        <b><u>"RULES\n"</u></b>
        <b>"1. "</b><i>"It will be a Group event.\n"</i>
        <b>"2. "</b><i>"Team can comprise of 8 - 10 members.\n"</i>
        <b>"3. "</b><i>"Duration: 10 Minutes.\n"</i>
        <b>"4. "</b><i>"The Judges decision will be final and binding to all."</i>
    </string>
    <string name="Kavyotsav">
        "Poetry, as they say is the language of the souls. And to enhance the evenings to a more graceful side, TheSoulWithin organises an assemblage of established poets wherein the eminent performers shall be touching the sects of Society, Religion, Love and Politics.\n\n"
        "Thus, an exposition of flowing emotions and flawlessness await all at:-\n"
        "#umango_ka_Pravah."
    </string>
    <string name="about">
        "It's the same game but this time it will be played differently, it won't be about victor or loser, it won't be about success or glory. This time it's about letting yourself flow in the PRAVAH of ebullience of UTTAR PRADESH lionising it's rich culture and heritage.\n"
        "As champions await, proclaim your throne.\n"
        "This time it will all be a quest for excellence.\n\n"
        "Let's flow in the PRAVAH of the exuberance of Uttar Pradesh and celebrate the carnival of AKTU's cultural fest happening in IET Lucknow. Come out and dive into the journey and experience a thrilling contest of the best talents from the state and encounter an amalgamation of the culture of Uttar Pradesh.\n\n"
        "Pravah encompasses lavish history, splendid culture and a profoundly rich heritage of Uttar Pradesh.\n\n"
        "The dates being 25th-27th March 2018, let us all plunge into a world made of the mystique of Uttar Pradesh and its budding talent. The team here at IET has strived hard to make Pravah a brilliant masterpiece of grandeur and transcendence.\n\n\n"
        "Welcome to PRAVAH, IET LUCKNOW."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">THEME</string>
    <string name="color">#000000</string>
    <string name="title_activity_band">Battle Of Bands</string>
    <string name="title_activity_play">Skit/Play</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fashion">Fashion Jalwa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_comedy">Mimicry/Standup Comedy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_singing">Singing(Solo, Duet, Group)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dance">Dance(Solo, Duet, Group)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_collage">Collage Making</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tshirt">T-shirt Painting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_poster">Poster Making</string>
    <string name="title_activity_face">Face Painting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rangoli">3D Painting/Rangoli</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mehandi">Mehandi Design</string>
    <string name="title_activity_alfaaz">Kavyotsav</string>
    <string name="title_activity_schedule">SCHEDULE</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sponcers">Sponcers</string>
</resources>
